laronne and welcome to another TV basics
laronne ，欢迎来到另一个电视基础知识
tutorial video in this video I'm gonna
这个视频中的教程视频我会
be showing you guys how we can get saved
向你们展示我们如何得救
from our paint screen back to our main
从 我们的油漆屏幕回到我们的主体
screen so before it was really easy
屏幕之前，它真的很容易
because we had just gigantic buttons but
因为我们只有巨大的按钮， 但是
now I want to actually impose another
现在我想实际施加另一个
button on this screen maybe a button
这个屏幕上的按钮可能是一个按钮
here that you know says go back home
在这里， 你知道说回家
okay and it looks better than that
好吧，它看起来 比这 更好
hopefully and we can click that and
希望，我们可以点击 和
actually go back home so that's our goal
其实回家 就是我们的目标
and so that's what we're going to be
所以这就是我们将 要成为的
doing in this video so anyways let's go
在这个 视频中 做反正 我们走吧
ahead get started so we don't actually
提前开始，所以我们 实际上 没有
have to change really anything here you
在这里你 必须 改变任何东西
might notice that I've changed lost my
可能会 注意到我已经改变了我的失败
mouse okay
老鼠没关系
I've changed this to main 3 now because
我已经将它更改为main 3，因为
it's another video for me but you might
这是 我 的 另一个视频，但你可能会
be following along in the same file the
继续 在 同一个文件中
whole time so uh here is my main 3
整个时间这么 呃这里是我的主要3
script and now to add a button we
脚本，现在添加一个按钮，我们
actually don't really need to touch
实际上并不需要碰触
anything more in here so I'm just going
更多在这里， 所以我只是去
to come down here and within another
在这里 和另一个 下来
screen we have painter and now what we
屏幕我们有画家，现在我们
can do though is we can also see the
可以做，但我们也可以看到
painter is basically just a widget okay
画家基本上只是一个小部件没关系
so we load in painter and then we'll
所以我们加载画家，然后我们会
load in a button easy enough
加载一个按钮很简单
this buttons gonna have a bunch of
这个按钮要去有一堆
parameters so the first parameter will
参数， 所以第一个参数会
be let's say color the color of the
让我们说颜色的颜色
button zero one zero one for lovely
按钮零一个零一个 可爱
green font size will say 25 size hints
绿色字体大小会说25个大小提示
this is basically just the size of the
这基本上只是大小
button according to the size of the page
按钮根据页面的大小
so 0.3 and 0.2 then we're gonna add some
所以0.3和0.2，然后我们会添加 一些
text on this button the text is gonna
文本就是这个按钮上的文本
say back home and then we're gonna say
说回家 ，然后我们会说
on underscore release and on release
下划线发布和发布
what do we want to do basically the same
我们想要做什么基本相同
thing as this button so I'm just
因为这个按钮，所以我只是
actually I copy and paste and instead of
实际上 我复制并 粘贴，而不是
other we want to go back to main so you
其他我们想回到主要所以你
might remember this from a couple videos
可能会从一些 视频中记住这一点
ago and then
之前和之后
we're going to position this using posts
我们将使用帖子对此进行定位
hint
暗示
in fact I forgot to add our float layout
实际上我忘了添加我们的浮动布局
dirt anyway post hints and we'll add
无论如何污点提示提示 ，我们将添加
this in four right whoops : 1 and then
这在四个正确的 哎呀： 1然后
top : 1 add your quotes here picture
顶部： 1在这里添加你的引用图片
spacing issues ok now what we also want
间距 问题 现在 确定 我们 还想要 什么
to do is our button is just a widget or
要做的是我们的按钮只是一个小部件 或
well okay the painter is just a widget
好吧，画家只是一个小部件
and so sort of is the button but we're
这样的按钮，但我们是
going to come down here and now we're
会在这里下来，现在我们
going to reference a floats layouts :
要引用浮动 布局：
and then within float layout we're gonna
然后在浮动布局内我们会
put the painter and the button the
把画家和按钮放在一边
painter widget enter button so let's go
画家小部件输入按钮，让我们走吧
ahead and save that now and let's run
提前保存 ，然后运行
that see how we do next screen now we've
看看我们现在如何做下一个屏幕
got our paint we'll just paint high and
得到我们的油漆， 我们只会画 高 和
then we can click back home we head back
那么我们可以点击回家我们回头
home and go back to next screen our
回家， 回到 下一个画面 我们
stuffs even still there fancy fancy
甚至还有花哨的花式
fancy okay well that's basically it for
看中好清楚 ，基本上它
adding the button to this screen just
添加按钮，这个屏幕的正
wanted to show a real simple example of
想表现的一个真实简单的例子
how to do it sometimes people ask me to
如何做到 这一点 ，有时人们问我
give them some challenges so I will give
给他们一些挑战，所以我会给
you a challenge and that will be now to
你是一个挑战， 现在将是
add a Clear button to the screen and
在屏幕上添加一个清除按钮
there's even some code online as far as
甚至还有一些代码在网上尽可能
how to do the clear you can go to the TV
如何清楚你可以去电视
website they actually have a paint
网站 他们实际上有一个油漆
application and they have a clear button
应用程序，他们有一个清晰的按钮
there you probably won't be able to
那你可能无法做到
superimpose that clear button really
叠加那个 清除 按钮
simply but there is a way to do it so I
简单但有办法做到这一点，所以我
encourage you to try to do it if you can
鼓励你 去 尝试，如果你能做到这一点
figure it out please try to post or
找 出来， 请尝试发布或
please post it here and share with the
请在这里发表， 并与分享
others if you figure out a good way to
其他如果你找出一个好办法
do it so anyways that's it for this
这样做， 以便反正就是它 这个
video
视频
if you guys have any questions or
如果你们有任何问题 或者
comments please feel free to leave them
评论请随时 离开他们
below otherwise as always thanks for
下面 另有一如既往感谢
watching things for all this board's
看所有这个委员会的东西
subscriptions and until next time
订阅，直到下一次